Guide to the W. Sterling Cole papers, [ca. 1935-1957]
Cole, W. Sterling papers
- Assorted Files, 1935-1954
  - Campaign Material Photographs, etc., Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Campaign 1937, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Political (Personal) Election Returns, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Convention, Republican (proposed) 1938, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Convention, Constitutional 1938, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Reapportionment 1937, 1942, 1937, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Campaign 1942, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Campaign 1942 Personal, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Campaign 1942, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Speeches, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Convention 1940, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Campaign 1940, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Campaign 1942, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 1954 Statement of Contributions and Expenditures, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Endorsements, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Congratulations - Primary and General - 1954, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 1954 General Election Returns (37th Congressional District), 1954 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Truth Shall Keep You Free - book (campaign materials), Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Campaign Material, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Len Hall File, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - General Aniline Co., Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Misc. Correspondence 1935-1954, 1935-1954 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Misc. Documents undated, Date Unknown (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous, Date Unknown (Box 12)
    Bath V.A. facility; R.R. Retirement; Steuben Co. T.B. Hospital
  - Old age pensions and compensation A-L, Date Unknown (Box 13)
  - Old age pensions and compensation M-Z, Date Unknown (Box 14)
  - Immigration A-Z, Date Unknown (Box 19)